[
    {
      "question": "_____が必要です。",
      "answer": "努力",
      "options": ["努力", "経験", "環境", "表現"]
    },
    {
      "question": "_____があります。",
      "answer": "経験",
      "options": ["発見", "経験", "状況", "努力"]
    },
    {
      "question": "新しい_____です。",
      "answer": "発見",
      "options": ["適当", "発見", "環境", "表現"]
    },
    {
      "question": "_____が大切です。",
      "answer": "環境",
      "options": ["努力", "環境", "表現", "状況"]
    },
    {
      "question": "この_____は難しい。",
      "answer": "表現",
      "options": ["経験", "状況", "表現", "適当"]
    },
    {
      "question": "_____が変わった。",
      "answer": "状況",
      "options": ["状況", "努力", "環境", "表現"]
    },
    {
      "question": "_____な答えです。",
      "answer": "適当",
      "options": ["適当", "発見", "表現", "経験"]
    },
    {
        "question": "これは____です。",
        "answer": "必要",
        "options": ["状況", "必要", "努力", "発見"]
      },
      {
        "question": "子どもが_____した。",
        "answer": "成長",
        "options": ["適当", "発見", "成長", "経験"]
      },
      {
        "question": "____があります。",
        "answer": "関係",
        "options": ["表現", "関係", "状況", "経験"]
      }
    ]